[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Розмова, діалог' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "呼びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Показувати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "話します"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Починати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "話し"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Пояснювати, повідомляти' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "見せます"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Адреса' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "始めます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Йти (опади)' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "教えます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Ім*я' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "住所"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Одразу' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "降ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Сіль' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "名前"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Цукор' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "直ぐ"
    }
]
